<root>
	<swf src="assets/flash/pic-text2.swf"/>
	<image src="assets/images/comfort/comfort.jpg">For Your Comfort</image>
	
	<heading>For Your Comfort</heading>
	<text><![CDATA[<h2>The Berkeley Dental Office</h2>
	
	<p>As an experienced dentist, Dr. Perez has been in the same location for over 25 years, and has served as a Berkeley dentist for over 25 years. This legacy of dental care has allowed us to get to know our patients well and make them part of our lives.</p>
	<p>We've seen the life-changing effect that cosmetic and restorative dentistry has provided for our patients over the years. In addition, because our patients appreciate a comfortable practice and relaxing environment, they're helped to continue their regular routine of care, without anxiety! </p>
	
	<p>Many have remarked that our dental office is more like coming to a spa. We've worked hard to remove the medicinal feel of traditional dental clinics. Therefore, we provide a number of amenities for your comfort. These include: </p>

<ul>
<li	>Neck pillows</li>
	<li>Cozy blankets</li>
	<li>Lumbar support pillows</li>
	<li>Padded chairs</li>
	<li>CD players</li>
	<li>Magazines</li>
	<li>Spring water</li>
	<li>Herbal tea</li>
	<li>Juices</li>
	<li>Nitrous oxide</li>
	<li>Video eyewear to watch movies</li>
</ul>
	
	<p>...and all provided in a home-like, warm, natural, comfortable setting. When you arrive, your care is our number one priority. You can always share with Dr. Perez and his dental team what we can do to help enhance your experience. </p>
	<p>Establishing and maintaining a patient safety standard that far exceeds government standards is also another goal we strive to achieve. We are committed to excellence in dentistry which also means excellence in patient safety and infection control. we have been certified by <b>Tom Terry Seminars</b> to make sure our standards are top-notch. To learn more, go to <a href="http://www.tomterryseminars.com/" target="_blank">http://www.tomterryseminars.com/</a>.</p>
	
	<p>Another benefit to patients is our convenient location. You will find the practice of cosmetic dentist Dr. Perez easy to find with close access to public transportation and BART lines. We also have parking right by the door, and there are no stairs or elevators for the ease of our patients.</p>
	<p>We welcome you to come and experience the special care and expertise that Dr. Perez and his team offer!</p>
	
	<br><br><br>]]></text>
</root>