<root>
	<swf src="assets/flash/pic-text2.swf"/>
	<image src="assets/images/services/healthy-bites.jpg">Healthy Bites</image>
	
	<heading>Healthy Bites</heading>
	<text><![CDATA[<p>An unhealthy bite may be the underlying cause of your aches and pains, discomfort or dental problems. 
Berkeley dentist Dr. Perez specializes in providing relief, and protecting your teeth and jaw health for the long-term. 
</p>
<p>Diagnosis and treatment begins when you and our TMJ-specialized dentist have discussed what the symptoms are that are causing you discomfort. This allows Dr. Perez to identify the source of your problem so it can be addressed, before they can worsen or cause other symptoms. 
</p>
<p>Is an unhealthy bite causing you pain? Here are some of the symptoms to consider: 
</p>
<ul><li>Do you wake up with sore, stiff or tired muscles around your jaws or front of your head? 
	</li><li>Do you have frequent headaches or neck aches? 
	</li><li>Is it painful to open your mouth, eat or yawn? 
	</li><li>Are you missing teeth? 
	</li><li>Are your teeth crooked or uneven? 
	</li><li>Have you or others noticed your teeth are short, worn, or with gaps? 
	</li><li>Have you ever cracked a tooth, filling or crown? 
	</li><li>Do you avoid chewing on one side of your mouth due to discomfort? 
	</li><li>Do you have teeth that no longer touch when you bite? 
	</li><li>Is it hard to use your front teeth to take bites of food? 
	</li><li>Do your teeth meet differently from time to time? 
	</li><li>Are you or others aware of any grinding or clenching of your teeth? 
	</li><li>Does your jaw click, pop, grate, or lock when you open your mouth? 
	</li><li>Have you noticed a change in your bite that bothers you or causes discomfort? 
</li></ul>
<p>"Bite Balancing" with this Berkeley dental team has key advantages, including: relieving painful symptoms, protecting your teeth and jaw health, and increasing the longevity of any cosmetic or restorative work. 
<a href="javascript: myLightWindow.activateWindow({href: 'dental-solutions/healthy-bites.html?template=lightwindow', title: '', type: 'external', width: '700', height: '900',  loadingAnimation: 'false'});" class="readmore"> READ MORE &#62;</a></p>
   <br><br><br>]]></text>
</root>