<root>
	<swf src="assets/flash/pic-text2.swf"/>
	<image src="assets/images/services/intro.jpg">Our Services</image>
	
	<heading>Our Services</heading>
	<text><![CDATA[<p><b>Our Unique Approach</b><br>Our number one focus is <i>you</i>... always <i>you</i>!

</p>
<p>Dr. Perez has made a conscious choice to work on ONE patient at a time, with plenty of time scheduled for YOU! Your treatment will NEVER be rushed.  You will always have Dr. Perez's undivided attention accompanied with plenty of time.  Attending to your concerns is always our top priority.
</p>
<p>Dr. Perez is passionate about staying on the leading edge of dental techniques and technology. Dr. Perez commits to an uncommon level of dedication to his patients care, which requires countless hours of study, travel, seminars, teaching, mentoring, and classes, with the best of the best in the dental profession.
</p>
<p>Proper diagnosis by Dr. Perez allows for individualized and precise treatment with effective, long-term solutions. We invite you to schedule a consultation with Dr. Perez to discuss what options can help bring out the best in your smile. Dental implants, TMJ treatment, hygiene, root canals, or beautiful porcelain crowns are just a few of the treatment options you can discuss during your one-on-one visit with Dr. Perez. 
</p>
<h3>Total Care Equals Total Health</h3>
<p>The teeth, gums, muscles and joints we use to talk and eat with are part of a very complex system that needs to work harmoniously together. The health, or ill-health, of any one of these systems, directly impacts the others. 
</p>
<p>Out-dated traditional dentistry, which uses a tooth-by-tooth approach to dental treatment, often leads to a short-term fix of problems without getting to their root cause. Many people have complex dental issues that may cause such symptoms as: 
</p>

	<ul><li>broken or cracked fillings 
		</li><li>chipped teeth 
		</li><li>joint aches in the jaw 
		</li><li>headaches 
		</li><li>teeth sensitivity 
		</li><li>bleeding gums 
		</li><li>pain when chewing
	</li></ul>
	
<p>It is important to diagnose and reverse these conditions. An ideal, healthy situation for optimum dental health and function is a stable, aligned bite; like balanced tires on a car that result in even wear on each tire. This smoothly working dental environment eliminates many problems and ensures the longevity of your natural teeth and any restorative treatments by our cosmetic dentist, Dr. Perez.
</p>
<p>We invite you to contact our El Cerrito dental office with any questions or comments about the cosmetic and restorative services we offer.
</p>
	
	<br><br><br>
	
	]]></text>
</root>